{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Fill in these idioms with the correct food or drink.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "apple",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "An _____ a day keeps the doctor away"
  }, {
    "answer": "potato",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Couch ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "milk",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Don't cry over spilled ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "lemonade",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "If life deals you lemons, make ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "eggs",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Don't put all your ____ in one basket"
  }, {
    "answer": "candy",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Like taking _____ from a baby"
  }, {
    "answer": "salt",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Take it with a grain of ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "wine",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Turn water into ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "cucumber",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "As cool as a ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "pancake",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "As flat as a _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Oil",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "___ and water don't mix"
  }, {
    "answer": "sliced bread",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "The greatest thing since ______ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "tea",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Not for all the ___ in China"
  }, {
    "answer": "pudding",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "The proof is in the _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "broth",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Too many cooks spoil the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "cake",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Let them eat ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "nut",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Tough ___ to crack"
  }, {
    "answer": "pie",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Humble ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "spice",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Variety is the _____ of life"
  }, {
    "answer": "bread",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Man does not live by _____ alone"
  }, {
    "answer": "coffee",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Wake up and smell the ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "vinegar",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "You'll catch more flies with honey than with _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Champagne",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "_________ taste on a beer budget"
  }, {
    "answer": "beans",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Not worth a hill of _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Beef",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "____, it's what's for dinner"
  }, {
    "answer": "Cream",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "_____ rises to the top"
  }, {
    "answer": "juices",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "Stew in one's own ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "carrot",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "The ______ and the stick"
  }, {
    "answer": "turnip",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "You can't squeeze blood from a ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "toast",
    "category": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
    "question": "The _____ of the town"
  }],
  "quizLength": 30,
  "title": "Sayings About Food Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/sayings-about-food-quiz.php"
}